export const data = [
    {
        question:"Which of the following command is used to create react-js-app ?",
        option1:"npx create-react-app appname",
        option2:"npm install create-react-app",
        option3:"npx install create-react-app -g",
        option4:"install - l create-react-app",
        ans:1,

    },
    {
        question:"In React.js which one of the following is used to create a class for Inheritance ?",
        option1:"Creates",
        option2:"Extends",
        option3:"Inherits",
        option4:"Delete",
        ans:2,
        
    },
    {
        question:"What is the default port number in which the application run ?",
        option1:"3000",
        option2:"8080",
        option3:"5000",
        option4:"3030",
        ans:1,
        
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following valid component return type of React ?",
        option1:"2",
        option2:"5",
        option3:"1",
        option4:"3",
        ans:3,
        
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is a way to handle data in React.js ?",
        option1:"State & Props",
        option2:"Services & Components",
        option3:"Services & Components",
        option4:"State & Component",
        ans:1,
        
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is must for the API in React.js ?",
        option1:"SetinitialComponent",
        option2:"renderComponent",
        option3:"render",
        option4:"All of the Above",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is true regarding Babel ?",
        option1:"Compiler",
        option2:"Transpilar",
        option3:"Both of the Above",
        option4:"None of the Above",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:"In React.js, how we can pass the data from one component to another in React.js ?",
        option1:"SetState",
        option2:"Render with Arguments",
        option3:"props",
        option4:"propTypes",
        ans:3,
        
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following function is true about changing the state in React.js ?",
        option1:"this.state {}",
        option2:"this.SetState",
        option3:"this.setChangeState",
        option4:"All of the above",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following method is true about referring parent class in React.js ?",
        option1:"self()",
        option2:"inherits()",
        option3:"this()",
        option4:"super()",
        ans:4,
    },
];